You will find that help will always be given at Hogwarts to those who ask for it.
Is this all real? Or is it just happening inside my head?
Of course it's happening inside your head, Harry.
Why should that mean that it's not real?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I'll never forget the first time I walked through those doors.
I never realized how beautiful this place was.
Yer a wizard, Harry.
I'm a what?
The ones that love us never really leave us. And you can always find them...in here.
Happiness can be found even in the darkest of times, if only one remembers to turn on the light.
Now the pain we all feel, but this dreadful loss reminds me — reminds us — while we may come from different places and speak in different tongues, our hearts beat as one.
But remember this. You have friends here. You're not alone.
Feels strange to be going home, doesn't it?
I'm not going home.
Not really.
Help will always be given at Hogwarts, Harry, to those who ask for it,
Help will always be given at Hogwarts to those who deserve it.